http://www.icsconnect.com/global-privacy-statement-overview

We use cookies and tracking technologies to offer you a better browsing experience, analyze site traffic, and improve the website.
By clicking “Accept Cookies”, you expressly agree to our use of cookies and tracking technologies in accordance with our Cookie Policy.
If you wish to prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics you can opt-out below.
Accept Cookies
Google Analytics Opt-Out
Our NetworkContactNews and Events
Privacy Statement Overview
AmerisourceBergen values and protects the personal information entrusted to the company by its suppliers, customers, and visitors. As a United States company doing business around the world, AmerisourceBergen maintains a comprehensive privacy program designed to comply with its legal obligations under applicable law. Because some requirements differ by jurisdiction, and in order to make this program as understandable as possible, AmerisourceBergen has divided its privacy notice into the following components:
Privacy Statement. This notice establishes the global baseline for AmerisourceBergen’s treatment of Personal Data, as defined under the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”). It applies to all users and includes some information that is specifically directed toward European users.
California Supplement. This supplemental notice adds to (and, in some cases, alters) the Privacy Statement with respect to users residing in California and Nevada.
Cookie Policy. This policy explains AmerisourceBergen’s use of cookies, web beacons, and related technologies.
Data Subject Requests (GDPR)
for EU residents
Make Request
Data Subject Requests (CCPA)
For California residents
Please review each component that applies to you. You may contact AmerisourceBergen with any questions concerning our privacy program at:
